<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Go on Armur</title>
    <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/tags/go/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Go on Armur</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:20:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://armur.ai/blogs/tags/go/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Using LLMs to Find Golang Vulnerabilities and Fixes </title>
      <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/using-llms-to-find-golang-vulnerabilities-and-fixes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:20:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/using-llms-to-find-golang-vulnerabilities-and-fixes/</guid>
      <description>Ensuring the security of software applications is becoming more important as technology evolves. Go, known for its simplicity and efficiency, is a popular choice for building high-performance applications. However, like any programming language, Go is prone to security vulnerabilities. Detecting and fixing these vulnerabilities early is crucial to safeguarding applications.&#xA;We will be using Armur which uses LLM Agents for Code Vulnerability Scanning. Armur is a platform designed to help developers find and fix security vulnerabilities in your code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability found in the ‘net’ package in Go and Rust.</title>
      <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/critical_vulnerability_found_in_the_net_package/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 09:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/critical_vulnerability_found_in_the_net_package/</guid>
      <description>The popular ‘net’ library used in GO and Rust was recently impacted by the mixed-format IP address validation vulnerability, a critical bug that made many applications extremely vulnerable. In this article, we will break it down and understand all about it.&#xA;Understanding the Vulnerability If you perform a simple search for &amp;ldquo;import net&amp;rdquo; on GitHub, it’ll reveal over 4 million files for Go alone relying on the net library, this means it’s a vulnerability of significant proportions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
