<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Devsecops on Armur</title>
    <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/tags/devsecops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Devsecops on Armur</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 13:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://armur.ai/blogs/tags/devsecops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Armur Ensures Safe Adoption of AI</title>
      <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/how_armur_helps_in_safe_adoption_of_ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 13:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/how_armur_helps_in_safe_adoption_of_ai/</guid>
      <description>How Armur Ensures Safe Adoption of AI The rise of Artificial Intelligence (AI) is revolutionizing industries across the globe, but with this rapid growth comes a set of new challenges—particularly in terms of security. As organizations increasingly adopt AI-driven solutions for everything from code generation to business process automation, ensuring the safe and secure use of AI becomes essential. Armur, with its advanced security tools and AI-driven capabilities, is at the forefront of making AI adoption safe, efficient, and reliable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Modern DevSecOps Culture</title>
      <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/how_to_build_a_modern_devsecops_culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 15:24:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/how_to_build_a_modern_devsecops_culture/</guid>
      <description>Technology has been evolving very rapidly, organizations face increasing pressure to deliver high-quality software quickly while maintaining robust security measures. This challenge has given rise to DevSecOps, a cultural and technical approach that integrates security practices into the DevOps workflow. DevSecOps isn&amp;rsquo;t just a set of tools or processes; it&amp;rsquo;s a fundamental shift in how teams think about and implement security throughout the software development lifecycle.&#xA;By embracing DevSecOps, companies can significantly reduce the risk of security breaches, improve compliance, and accelerate the delivery of secure software.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
