<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blockchain on Armur</title>
    <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/tags/blockchain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blockchain on Armur</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 15:20:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://armur.ai/blogs/tags/blockchain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is Front Running and MEV?</title>
      <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/what-is-front-running-and-mev/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 15:20:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/what-is-front-running-and-mev/</guid>
      <description>Front-running in Blockchain occurs when someone intentionally enters a transaction into a block before you to try to extract some value. Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re at a high-stakes auction, bidding on a rare artifact. Just as you&amp;rsquo;re about to place your bid, someone with inside information swoops in, outbids you, and resells the item at a profit moments later. This is the essence of front running in the crypto space, but with far-reaching implications for market integrity and individual traders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Botnets The Good, The Bad, and The Secure</title>
      <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/decentralized_botnets_the_good_the/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 18:31:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/decentralized_botnets_the_good_the/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to the Wild, Wild Web! A place where the digital gold rush meets the cyber outlaws, and the sheriffs are armed with nothing but code. In this thrilling expanse, there&amp;rsquo;s a new player in town: decentralized botnets. Imagine a swarm of drones, each with its own mind, yet united in purpose, buzzing through the digital skies. Some are here to protect the town, while others have more nefarious plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Role of AI in Preventing DDoS Attacks on Blockchain Networks</title>
      <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/the_role_of_ai_in_preventing_ddos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 18:31:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/the_role_of_ai_in_preventing_ddos/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the vast digital ecosystem, where threats evolve at breakneck speed, a revolutionary approach is making waves: swarm learning. This isn&amp;rsquo;t your ordinary tech trend; it&amp;rsquo;s a paradigm shift inspired by nature itself. Just like flocks of birds move in harmony or schools of fish pivot to evade predators, swarm learning harnesses the power of collective intelligence to fortify our digital defenses.&#xA;Imagine a network of computers learning from each other in real-time, sharing insights and strategies without a central command, each node contributing to a more resilient and adaptive security system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Web3 Cybersecurity Challenges</title>
      <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/understanding_web3_cybersecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 18:31:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/understanding_web3_cybersecurity/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: The New Frontier of Web3 As we stand on the brink of a digital revolution, the emergence of Web3 heralds a transformative era for the internet as we know it. This new phase, characterized by decentralization, blockchain technologies, and a push towards user sovereignty, redefines our interactions online, promising a future where users have unprecedented control over their data and digital identities.&#xA;Web3, in essence, represents a shift from centralized platforms, where data is stored in servers owned by a handful of corporations, to a decentralized network, built on the principles of blockchain technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Future: Predicting the Next Big Revolution in Blockchain and AI</title>
      <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/unlocking_the_future_predicting_the/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 18:31:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/unlocking_the_future_predicting_the/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Imagine having a magic mirror rather than a crystal ball, one that doesn&amp;rsquo;t just predict the future but actively shapes it, especially in the realms of Blockchain and Artificial Intelligence (AI). That&amp;rsquo;s exactly the role we&amp;rsquo;ve embraced here at Armur AI. Far from being mere spectators, we&amp;rsquo;re at the vanguard, merging the formidable powers of AI and Blockchain to redefine cybersecurity&amp;rsquo;s landscape.&#xA;Blockchain and AI, each a behemoth in its own right, have begun to converge in ways that promise to amplify their individual strengths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity in the IoT Era How Blockchain &amp; AI Shield Your Devices</title>
      <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/cybersecurity_in_the_iot_era_how_blockchain_ai_shield_your_devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/cybersecurity_in_the_iot_era_how_blockchain_ai_shield_your_devices/</guid>
      <description>Ah, the Internet of Things (IoT) &amp;mdash; that futuristic concept we all dreamed about is now a tangible reality, connecting everything from your fridge to your car. But with great connectivity comes great responsibility, or in this case, a massive cybersecurity headache. As our devices chatter away, they open doors to potential cyber threats. Enter the dynamic duo of blockchain and artificial intelligence (AI). These technologies are not just reshaping the cybersecurity landscape; they&amp;rsquo;re redefining it, with pioneers like Armur AI leading the charge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Blockchain Security Checklist by Armur AI</title>
      <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/the_blockchain_security_checklist_armur_ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/the_blockchain_security_checklist_armur_ai/</guid>
      <description>In the digital era, where blockchain technology is as revolutionary as it is complex, the armor of cybersecurity needs to be as unbreachable as possible. With cyber threats morphing faster than a chameleon on a rainbow, safeguarding the integrity and security of blockchain networks is more crucial than ever. Armur AI, standing tall as a beacon in the AI-driven cybersecurity landscape, unveils its master blueprint: The Blockchain Security Checklist. Consider this your compass in the vast sea of blockchain technology, guiding you through the stormy waters of cyber threats with wisdom gleaned from the very forefront of industry expertise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Privacy in Blockchain Applications</title>
      <link>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/the_importance_of_privacy_in_blockchain_applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://armur.ai/blogs/posts/the_importance_of_privacy_in_blockchain_applications/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the realm of blockchain technology, a paradox exists at its very core: the need for both transparency and privacy. On one hand, blockchain&amp;rsquo;s transparency is lauded for its ability to offer unparalleled visibility into transactions, fostering trust among users. On the other, this very openness poses significant privacy concerns, revealing transaction details that users might prefer to keep private. This tension between transparency and privacy raises an essential question: How can blockchain applications maintain their inherent security and openness while also protecting the privacy of their users?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
