<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Armur</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/tags/armur/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Armur</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 15:01:35 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blogs/tags/armur/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Armur’s Role Against Zero-Day Exploits in AI-Generated Code</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/posts/armur_against_zero_days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/posts/armur_against_zero_days/</guid>
      <description>What Are Zero-Day Exploits? A zero-day exploit is a cyberattack that capitalizes on a previously unknown vulnerability in software, hardware, or firmware. These vulnerabilities, referred to as zero-day vulnerabilities, are flaws that have not been discovered or patched by the developer or vendor. The term “zero day” signifies that there is zero time to fix the issue before it is exploited by attackers.&#xA;When a hacker identifies and uses a zero-day vulnerability to breach systems, this is called a zero-day attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Are Code Vulnerability Scanning Tools?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/posts/what_are_code_vulnerability_scanning_tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 09:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/posts/what_are_code_vulnerability_scanning_tools/</guid>
      <description>In today’s digital landscape, security is important. As organisations increasingly rely on software to drive their operations, the risk of cyberattacks has grown. Code vulnerability scanning tools have become essential in the fight to protect sensitive data, maintain operational integrity, and safeguard against breaches. This article explains what code vulnerability scanning tools are, how they work, their importance, and the key features that make them important in modern software development and security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does A Static Code Analysis Tool Work?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/posts/how_static_analysis_works/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/posts/how_static_analysis_works/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Static code analysis is an essential process in software development, enabling developers to analyze the structure of code without executing it. This method is widely used to detect security vulnerabilities, bugs, and other defects in software, making it a crucial step in ensuring the quality and security of applications. This article gets into the mechanics of static code analysis, the underlying technology that makes it possible, and the limitations that come with this approach.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
